Consumption
A sun and their sun are rising
and the air brings augment their waters
In a day of the simple skies came to dance
How can the song play to the day?
Think about it.
You may want the night out.
There is a backdrop of seeing nothing wanna show you.
No, not the Deucalion. But why would they...
They had no other option but to make a frontal assault.
Control, come in! Mustang Leader calling!
Please respond!
Princess One, acknowledge!
Your Highness, you okay?
Huh?
I've located the Princess. She seems to be alive.
This is control to Mustang Platoon. Do you copy?
Lieutenant Marito!
Is that Amifumi?
Is the Deucalion all right? Is everyone on the bridge okay?
What about Nina and Kom? Are they okay?
I think so. We're okay. Might not be entirely accurate. More like one of those, we'll let you know later. You go on without us now kind of deals.
Yinko, I'm sorry.
Warrant Officer Kaisuka, continue the Princess One mission. Can you do that?
Yes.
Amifumi. Young Kaisuka. You cover Warrant Officer Kaisuka. Will do.
Yes, sir.
Warrant Officer Kaisuka, taking the pilot's seat. Princess One, continuing the mission.
Kick their asses for us.
Mustang 2-2 here. Roger that.
Are you awake?
Huh?
It's probably going to get a little bumpy back there. So hold on tight, Your Highness.
You are the older sister of Inaho.
You didn't seem to be badly hurt, but I only made a quick check. Let me know if I missed something, okay?
Why would you...
You must hate us, don't you?
Huh?
We Versians who did this. We damaged the Earth and took so many lives.
How could you not hate us?
Salem.
What does it take to end a war? Do you know?
Well, if both sides set aside hatred, peace can then be reached.
No.
Huh?
It is a fact. Warfare is just a form of negotiation. It is not dependent upon hate.
Territory or resources someone wants for themselves. Ideology, religion, pride. Wars are fought for those objectives all the time. And once those objectives have been met, the war comes to an end.
Either that, or the war will end when the overall human cost outweighs the gains.
Anger and hatred are nothing more than tools used to tilt a war in someone's favor. And I am not interested in those emotions.
Oh, we know.
So therefore, just because someone is a Martian is no reason for me to hate them.
Hmm.
Really, I am happy to hate Terrans just for being bored.
All units, scatter!
Please make peace with your creator, your highness.
All of this time it was you? Count Sazbomb, why?
Our comms are encrypted. How do you tap in?
All units, further communication by laser comms only.
Yuki, continue the mission. Inko, you provide support for Yuki.
I'll stay and hold this guy off.
Don't be stupid. You don't know what his combat capability is. You can't win this alone.
I don't need to win. I only need to slow him down.
Hinaho!
You're not planning to be some kind of human shield, are you?
No. That's not an effective way to buy us time. Now go!
Wait, Hinaho!
Good luck out there.
Thank you.
Let's move out! Yes, ma'am!
Oh, Hinaho.
I admire your reckless valor, Terran warrior. But you will have no mercy for me!
Using decoys will confuse guided missiles, but rockets without a target guidance system will not be affected.
Mustangs one, one, one! Path secured!
Mustangs one, one! Path secured!
Don't be too proud of yourself, Terran. Light of old Noah, actuate!
Don't be too proud of yourself, Terran! Light of old Noah, actuate!
Oh, my lady.
Give me your strength!
And now behold...
The Dioscuria!
What? My rounds, they just...
Dimensional barrier is activated.
Energy junctions are fully linked.
Field generator is functional.
Blade field engaged.
Blade is drawn.
That weapon.
Is the princess aboard that ship?
No, she's not.
Attention, Oldenburg leader here.
Coming to assist Mustang 2-2.
No, fall back. Don't engage.
You stupid fools.
Fly!
Go, my servant!
Count Sosbaum.
Surrender, Martian. Put your hands above your head.
Come on!
Terran troops have gotten into the castle.
We need more defenders.
How'd you save me back there?
Huh?
Even though you know that I'm a Terran.
Who are you just fighting against?
Who are you pointing your gun at back there?
I don't see anyone here aiming at his friends.
So stop asking these stupid questions.
Damn, one of them got in.
Sounds like it's starting up.
We need to alert the Cap-Latoon inside the castle.
Initiating auxiliary power.
Let's see if it works.
No such luck.
The Alt-Noah Drive's been shut down.
This Cataphract won't be taking me anywhere without someone to activate the drive.
So what should I do?
What's going on?
The Alt-Noah Drive just powered up.
But how could it?
Is it too much to ask for them to just give it a rest with those things?
There is another passageway.
It is a detour, but it will take us to the Alt-Noah Chamber.
It was not intended for large machinery, so we must abandon our cataphracts and proceed on foot.
You there, Mustang-1-1?
Yes, ma'am.
Let's do this.
Roger.
I-Inaho?
Hello, Princess Asalem.
Your life, if you please.
Count Sosbaum, why are you doing this?
You bastard!
He has a barrier, too!
Inko, get out of here!
Inaho!
Hurry up, go!
No way!
I can't just leave you!
Don't worry about me, just go!
Don't be an idiot!
Dodge it!
Mustang-1-1!
Just like I thought, any time he launches his arms, he has to lower the barrier first, because the arm thrusters interfere with the barrier.
Now hold on!
You'd use me for a decoy?
So that's how it works, huh?
The barrier needs to have a gap.
If you're watching closely, it's pretty easy to spot right at the instant he raises the field.
For the flying arms, the remote control antenna!
You've tried my patience!
Now, get out of there!
I can't.
I've been waiting for him to get close enough.
You wretched!
And also, the barrier can't be on a contact surface.
Why you...
Let's count Sazbom!
I can't hit him!
How can it dodge like that?
It's like it's anticipating the path of our bullets!
Perfectly!
Princess, come on!
We need to hurry!
I'm right here!
You too, Inaho!
I get.
You go on ahead.
I'll be close behind.
Please lead the way, your highness.
All right, of course.
This way!
Filthy Terran.
How dare you!
Damn you!
With your ignorance, you could never understand!
The envy and hatred planted in us against you Terrans was a tarnish on our souls, denying us the ability to live as human beings!
You, with your indolent lives in a land of plenty, could not possibly ever comprehend how that feeling festered in us!
Knowing hatred is being forced into you, and the sense of futility when you realize it,
the pain of failing to protect the one you love, you could never understand!
Count Sospo!
Orange, it's you!
Go on!
We'll hold them off for you!
Hurry!
Optical Seeker powering down.
Auxiliary sensor feed to main monitor.
Right arm, power cut.
Left arm only.
I swear, I will defeat all those whom I hate.
And I shall break this cycle of hatred.
In the name of Asalem vs. Ellusia!
Killed Sospo!
Power down!
Fire!
Where are you, my lord?
Inaho, no!
Are you alright?
Princess of Salem...
Salem, is that you?
Inaho, you're alive. Thank goodness.
I have shut down the Landing Castle's old Noah Drive.
The operation was a success. Now we should escape.
I'm sorry, Salem. Can't see very well. I have blood in my eyes.
I'm right here, Inaho.
Let me help you. Everything's fine.
My Lord Sosbalm, what did you do?
Guess the sun has saved me too. Thank you, Slane.
I... I...
Quite well done.
Haaaaas!
Haaaaaas!!
Don't!
Hmph.
I don't know.
Don't.
That is far enough.
Do not touch her highness.
Orange.
Oh, bat.
Bad.
I don't know.
Count Sosbohm's landing castle, which had attacked Earth headquarters, had fallen.
The battle ended in victory for the United Forces of Earth.
There were many casualties on both sides.
The whereabouts of Royal Princess of Salem Versa Lucia of Verse are still unknown.
They arrived here, which of M нав fantasies.
Yeah.
Wow.
Yeah, just to her.
Well, yeah.
Thank you.